So what you're about to witness should actually have a disclaimer because the way this man
take this man down is an act of violence. Intellectual violence. You're going to watch
President Ali of Guyana. This reporter who feel as though he can lecture Guyana on climate change.
Now don't get me wrong. I like when press politically presses but so often we are seeing
journalists. Some for the truth of everyone but other white people. Especially Zionists.
So I want you to just take it in and enjoy this exemplification of knowledge of your environment
and your nation. It's expected that there will be 150 billion dollars worth of oil and gas extracted
off your coast. That means according to many experts more than 2 billion tons of carbon emissions
will come from your seabed from those reserves and be released into the atmosphere. I don't know if
you as a head of state went to the COP in Dubai. Let me stop you right there. Let me stop you right
here. Do you know that Guyana has a forest that is the size of England and Scotland combined? A forest
that stores 19.5 gigatons of carbon? A forest that we have kept alive? A forest that we have kept alive?
Does that give you the right? Does that give you the right to release all of this carbon?
Does that give you the right to lecture us on climate change? I am going to lecture you on climate change
because we have kept this forest alive that stores 19.5 gigatons of carbon that you enjoy,
that the world enjoy, that you don't pay us for, that you don't value, that you don't see a value in,
that the people of Guyana has kept alive. Guess what? We have the lowest deforestation rate in the world.
And guess what? Even with our greatest exploration of the oil and gas resource we have now,
we will still be net zero. Guyana will still be net zero. With all our exploration,
couple of points. We'll still be net zero. No, no, no. Powerful, powerful words, Mr. President.
I'm not completed as yet. I am not finished as yet. I am just not finished as yet. Because this is
the hypocrisy that exists in the world. We, the world in the last 50 years has lost 65% of all its
biodiversity. We have kept our biodiversity. Are you valuing it? Are you ready to pay for it? When is
the developed world going to pay for it? Or are you in the pockets? Are you in the pockets of those who have
damaged the environment? Are you in the pockets? Are you in your system in the pockets of those who
destroyed the environment through the industrial revolution and now lecturing us? Are you in their
pockets? Are you paid by them? There is no hypocrisy in our position.
Support a real one.